subitup.com 2011-11-30

# SubItUp

## Privacy Policy

SubItUp provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of this website, located at www.SubItUp.com ("Site") or collected through our job shift exchange service, including via SMS ("Service"). This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

By using our Site you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing" means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the U.S. your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the U.S., and processed and stored there under U.S. privacy standards. By visiting our Site and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to, and processing in, the US.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at privacy@SubItUp.com. 

## Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting personally identifiable information are to provide you with the product and services made available through the Site, including, but not limited to the Service, to communicate with you, and to manage your registered user account, if you have one.

__Information Collected Upon Registration__ If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site, you will be required to become a registered user, and to submit certain personally identifiable information to SubItUp. This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for the Service, or if you desire to receive SMS alerts and updates. Personally identifiable information that we may collect in such instances may include your IP address, full user name, password, email address, city, time zone, telephone number, and other information that you decide to provide us with.

__Additional Information__ If you activate the mobile phone options per the Terms of Service at www.SubItUp.com/tos, we will collect your cellular phone number. You will receive notifications on your cellular phone in a small number of cases, such as when a coworker requests to switch shifts with you. If you contact us by email through the Site, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you.

__Use of Contact Information__ In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about our products and services, including but not limited to our Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

__Log Data__ When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site’s technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

__Service Providers__ We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.

__Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement__ SubItUp cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of SubItUp or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

## Changing or Deleting Information

You can update or access your personal information via your account home page and may change any of that information at any time. You may also close your account with SubItUp at any time. 

## Security

SubItUp is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

## Links to Other Websites

Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.
